- ↑ Shlomo Eliraz 3, Rishon LeZziyon
- **\** 052-8088727
- in Gal Wainberg
- Gal-wainberg.com

# **Gal Wainberg**

I am Electrical and Electronics Engineering student on fourth year, specialization in DSP. I am highly responsible with prioritize capabilities, manage my tasks to meet project timeline, and keep always to remain organized. I am an effective team player focused with the team to accomplish task objectives, costumer facing skills and highly communicated person. Willing to explore my knowledge in electronics Network, RF, Integration, R&D and Validation & Verification.

## **Employment History**

#### Network Operation Center / TATA – TCS, 2019-present

NOC operator in charge of monitoring, controlling and operating computer system, data analysis and troubleshooting. Access to core systems and communication such as Virtual machines and SFTP. Certified as operator of Control M and Centerity automation programs – systems support for application and technical teams.

#### Integrator & Customer support /ELTA - IAI, 2015-2017

Experienced System Integration Specialist with demonstrated experience in aviation and aerospace industry. Especially of the field of radar system, RF, Fiber optics, System Engineering and Embedded System. Experienced with relevant testis equipment as part of my ongoing role as part of integration team. In addition, ongoing support for IDF for full troubleshooting support.

#### **Education**

### Electrical & Electronics engineering / Azrieli College of Engineering, 2017-present

B.Sc. Electrical & Electronics engineering student on fourth year.

Specialization in DSP (Digital Signal Processing).

#### **Electronics studies /ORT Aviation and Aerospace College, 2008-2011**

Graduated of Air Force Academy

- Full matriculation majoring in Electronics.
- Technology certificate with specialization in Electronics and Computer science.

## Military service

#### Mandatory and Career service, 2011-2015

Service as an "Iron Dome" level A & B radar technician and team leader. Graduated rank as Sergeant Major.

#### Other skills:

- Prog': C++, VHDL, MATLAB,
  Python
- Radio Frequency

#### **Languages:**

Hebrew: mother tongue

- Integration
- Fiber Optics
- Control M
- Quick and self-learner
- Troubleshooting
- Customer support

• English: High level